Katherine Ferreyra

Technical Writer

Highly organized and accomplished technical writer with experience in writing and editing user-end and internal engineering technical documents, including user guides, design specifications, and correlation/compliance reports. Quick to learn new authoring programs and content management systems. Social collaborator to gather technical information from subject matter experts (SMEs) to write concise and accurate documentation.

katferreyra@outlook.com

in linkedin.com/in/katferreyra



Remote - CA, United States



katferreyra.github.io

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Technical Writer Marvell Technology, Inc.

04/2024 - Present

Senior Technical Writer Marvell Technology, Inc.

07/2021 - 03/2024

Santa Clara, CA

- Collaborate with SMEs in various time zones to obtain and ensure accurate and updated content.
- Author and edit internal and external design specifications, application notes, and correlation reports.
- Push documentation through each step of the release flow to meet design release dates.
- Edit and publish internal engineering newsletter for companywide distribution.

Technical Writer II Synopsys

12/2020 - 07/2021

Mountain View, CA

- Supported documentation for 7 products, including user guides, release notes, and customer training slides.
- Led core team meetings to advocate for accurate technical content in documentation.
- Updated product documentation through internal release management system.
- Edited man pages for grammar and technical issues, such as missing or inaccurate information.

Technical Writer I **Synopsys**

05/2019 - 12/2020

Mountain View, CA

- Supported documentation for 4 products, including user guides, release notes, customer training slides.
- Documented new features through release notes and user guide updates for every service pack and major release.
- Coordinated with SMEs to ensure accurate technical features and usage examples for end users.
- Peer reviewed and edited user guides and release notes for every release.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

B.A. Professional, Technical, Business, and Scientific Writing

San José State University

2017 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

Marvell: Received Execution Excellence Award (03/2023 - 03/2023)

Received recognition for producing quality deliverables to customer commitments as scheduled by program management.

Synopsys: Joined Man Page Editing Initiative (03/2021 - 07/2021)

Volunteered to take on additional responsibilities to review man pages. Edit syntax for technical clarity and grammar, while adhering to the publication style guide.

Synopsys: Published eLearning Module (07/2020 - 09/2020)

Created an eLearning module published for customers to learn about the supported product. Compiled marketing information and SME input to produce an introduction course. Used Articulate Storyline to design the UX and audio input.

Synopsys: Participated in DITA Testing (09/2019 - 09/2019)

Learned DITA in oXygen XML Editor in 3 weeks. Converted 7 user guides from Adobe FrameMaker to oXygen XML Editor by hard deadline.